Once you've learned how to pars JSON data, it's pretty
straight forward to be able to pars the rest of the
fields that we need. Since this isn't a course on
Java or JSON, we're going to provide you with the parsing
code in the gist below. And this is what the
gist looks like. There are three helper methods. The first is
for formatting dates. The second is for rounding temperatures. The third
is for turning a forecastJsonStr, into an array of weather forecasts.
Update the Fetch Weather Tasks to use these helpful functions. And
the do in background method should return a string array of
forecasts. You can log the output to check that the array
is correct. The format of one day's forecast should look like this.